<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TaapApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_taap">About TAAP</string>
    <string name="taap_consultancy">TAAP Consultancy</string>
    <string name="driving_digital_transformation">DRIVING DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION</string>
    <string name="consultancy">CONSULTANCY</string>
    <string name="consultancy_text">WHY TAAP? \nIf you have decided your organisation wants to embrace No-Code as a technology, you need to assess which provider to utilise. At the time of writing there are over 450 No-Code / Low-Code product vendors, many focus narrowly on delivering superb functionality, or are limited in their deployment configurations. For example, clients can’t create private instances; the product is mobile-only; the product doesn’t work offline, or only runs on a specific platform i.e. iOS or Android, not PCs and Tablets etc.\n\nTAAP The Agile Application has been focused on the build and delivery of No-Code powered applications since 2003. We support all device form factors, operating systems, online and offline, integration to back end systems, hard real-time systems, third party integrations, custom extensions, and much more. We also support all non functional requirements from support version management, debugging, integration, instrumentation to help manage and deploy solutions at scale.\n\nWe have extensive experience of deploying this technology into every industry, vertical and in multiple languages. We don’t just provide the software, our own consultancy teams use it to deliver solutions that operate for the largest of global enterprises 24x7x365.\n\nWith fewer developers in the market today, Pro developers are now a bottle neck for delaying digital transformation projects on time. No-Code platforms like ours focuses on domain experts and citizen development. We believe No-Code software shouldn’t limit functionality or organisations to move into a hyper agile development culture.\n\nNo-Code is an extremely powerful technology. If you are adopting a platform, choose an organisation that has over 18 years of experience delivering and deploying this technology. TAAP use best practices to collate and store digital data so that it can be interpreted and analysed using tools and techniques which provide organisations with valuable insights into their operations.\n\nWith Gartner predicting by 2024 at least 65% of all new business applications will be created using citizen developers, now is the time to review how your business can leverage the power of No-Code technology.</string>
    <string name="about_texts">OUR MISSION \nWe deliver new and innovative ways to undergo digital transformation.\n\nOur core principle is to provide hyper agile delivery through a ‘configure not code’ approach.\n\nWe don’t just talk about No-code we help organisations see this technology come to life, using plain English but driven from the perspective of business and operational best practices.\n\nDelayed development, costly builds or software acquisition, before long the new system becomes like other old legacy systems.\n\nFundamentally the landscape of change management projects are changing. The gap between business analysts, development build and end users, there is always a disconnect. Low-Code and citizen development narrows the gap for not only miscommunication between teams but hyper agile development from the start.\n\nHere is where TAAP has been changing the way software is not only developed but reducing implementation time, full integration with current software, and the ability to change and expand applications all while reducing costs.\n\n</string>
</resources>